你们男生不懂亲吻对女生的重要性
You don't understand.
对我们而言，亲吻和其他任何部分一样重要
For us,kissing is as important as any part.
没错
Yeah,right!
当真?
You serious?
当然
Oh,yeah.
- 你想了解的一切全在初吻之中  - 没错
- Everything is in that first kiss. - Absolutely.
对我们而言亲吻就像是开场
For us,kissing's an opening act..
就像平克・弗洛伊德乐队出场前
like the comedian you have to sit through..
你得耐着性子先看完滑稽表演
before Pink Floyd comes out.
对，我们并非讨厌滑稽表演
And it's not that we don't like the comedian.
只是那不是我们买票的原因
It's just that that's not why we bought the ticket.
问题在于演唱会结束后 不论表演有多精采
The problem is,no matter how great the show was..
你们女生总还想再看滑稽表演
you girls are looking for the comedian again.
我们在车上奋力与交通阻塞战斗  只是拼命保持清醒
We're in the car,fighting traffic,just trying to stay awake.
给你一个建议 回去拉上滑稽表演者
Word of advice: Bring back the comedian.
否则下次，你们只能坐家里听唱片
Or next time you'll find yourself listening to that album alone.
我们还在谈论性吗?
Are we still talking about sex?
六人行 第1季 第02集 超声波检查
The One With the Sonogram at the End
不，这样很好
No,it's good. It is good.
只是她看起来是不是有点生气吗?
It's just that Doesn't she seem a little angry?
她有麻烦事
Well,she has issues.
她有吗?
Does she?
她尝试和“参与者先生”生活在一起
Try to live with "Mr. I'm Evolving."
他在外头乱搞女人而她在家里设法去除地毯上乳齿象的味道
He's out while she's home getting the mastodon smell out of the carpet.
玛莎，他们是穴居人
Marsha,see,these are cave people.
他们关心的问题是
Okay,they have issues like:
吉，那条冰河愈来愈接近了
"Gee,that glacier's getting kind of close."
谈到麻烦事，那不是你前妻吗?
Speaking of issues,isn't that your ex-wife?
- 不，那不是  - 是的，是卡萝，嗨
- No. - Yes,it is. Carol,hi!
好吧，是她 我会到冰河期去找你
Okay. Yes,it is. I'll catch up with you in the Ice Age.
- 我可以留在这吗？  -不
- Can I stay? - No.
- 嗨. - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 我来的时间不对？ - 不，这里是…
- Is this a bad time? - No,it's..
石器时代
the Stone Age.
你的气色好极了，我讨厌看到这样
You look great. I hate that.
抱歉，谢了！你的气色也很好
Sorry. Thanks. You look good too.
好吧，在这儿任何人
Well,you know,in here,anyone who..
直立行走的人…
stands erect..
- 最近如何? 还是… - 女同志?
- What's new? Still a - A lesbian?
那是你都不知道的 家庭生活如何?
You never know. How's the family?
- 玛蒂的疑心病还是很重  - 卡萝，为什么来这儿?
- Marty's still totally paranoid. - Carol,why are you here?
- 我怀孕了  - 怀孕
- I'm pregnant. - Pregnant.
她似乎不急着离开
She didn't leave in such a hurry after all.
这是“斯瑞家族公司”，他们有误会的那集
This is the Three's Company episode with a misunderstanding.
我看过这一集
Then I've already seen this one.
喝完没?
Are you through with that?
抱歉，吞下去的时间太慢
Sorry,the swallowing slowed me down.
这是谁的小纸团?
Whose ball of paper is this?
我的，我写给自己一张便条 后来觉得自己不需要
Mine. I wrote a note to myself,then I didn't need it.
于是将它揉成纸团 现在我不想活了
So I balled it up and now I wish I was dead.
她已经拍松过那个枕头.  莫妮卡，你已经拍过了枕头了
She already fluffed that pillow. You already fluffed It's fine.
我只是不想让他们有借题发挥的机会
I just don't wanna give them any more ammunition.
我们都知道父母对枕头平的孩子有多凶
Parents can be cruel about the flatness of a child's pillow.
放松一下，你每次都这样  这里看起来已经很棒了
Relax,you do this every time. The place looks great.
你这里有意大利烤宽面 这看起来好极了
You got a lasagna here that looks good enough..
还不许碰
to avoid touching.
莫妮卡？嗨！
Monica? Hi!
莫妮卡…你吓到我了
Monica,you're scaring me.
我是说，你现在这样子慌慌张张的
I mean,you're all chaotic and twirly,you know?
显得不是很好
Not in a good way.
安心吧.没看过每次他们来时罗斯会慌张
Calm down. You don't see Ross getting twirly every time they come.
因为在我爸妈心目中罗斯不可能犯错
That's because my parents think Ross can do no wrong.
他是个王子
You see,he's "The Prince."
显然,他们在我出生前有个大型仪式
They had some big ceremony before I was born.
什么? - 丑陋裸男有个“美腿器”
- What? - Ugly Naked Guy got a ThighMaster.
- 有人看见我的订婚戒指吗?  - 有，很漂亮
- Has anybody seen my engagement ring? - It's beautiful.
天啊! 天啊! 天啊! 糟了
Oh,God! Oh,God! Oh,God!
嘿,不要动它们
No,don't touch that.
明天就要还他戒指 我似乎还不够担心
Like I wasn't dreading tomorrow enough,having to give it back.
“贝瑞，记得我吗?我是那个穿白纱让你在亲友面前出糗的人”
"Hi,Barry,remember me? I'm the girl that stomped on your heart."
天啊，如今我必须还他戒指 偏偏戒指不见了
Now I must return the ring without the ring..
局面更糟糕了
which makes it so much harder.
别急，我们会找到的，对不对?
Easy,we'll find it. Won't we?
一切都会好的，我们会把它找回来的
Look,it's gonna be okay. You'll give it back..
-而且我们会吃冰淇淋 -好吧，是一个珍珠型的钻石
- and we'll eat ice cream. - Okay. It's a pear-shaped diamond
不管我们找到什么样的钻石戒指都会给你的
Any diamond ring we find,we'll run it by you.
- 最后一次戴是在什么时候?  -狗崽儿，大概是在遗失之前
- When did you have it last? - Doy,right before she lost it.
这年头说狗崽儿的人不多
You don't get a lot of "doy" these days.
我今天早上还戴它
I know I had it this morning.
我戴着它在厨房跟…
I know I had it when I was in the kitchen with
戴娜在一起?
Dinah?
- 别生气 - 你不会
- Oh,don't be mad. - You didn't.
- 对不起  - 我就让你做了这么一件事情
- Oh,I'm sorry. - I gave you one job!
你看面条现在变得多直
But look how straight those noodles are.
莫妮卡，在意大利烤宽面中找订婚戒指不是那样找的
That's not how you look for an engagement ring in a lasagna.
我办不到
I just can't do it.
孩子们，我们上场
Boys? We're going in.
嗨
Hi.
- 这可不是开心的“嗨”  - 卡萝怀孕了
- That is not a happy "hi." - Carol's pregnant.
我找到了
I found it!
什,什,什么?
What?
是的
Yeah.
你再持续两小时,就会变成我这样
Do that for two hours,you might be where I am about now.
如此一来,枕头的事就可先放在一旁了
That puts that whole pillow thing in perspective.
你现在要怎么办?
How do you fit into this whole thing?
卡萝说她和苏珊想让我加人
Carol and Susan want me to be involved.
但是对这件事我不太感到舒服,我不想卷进去
But if I'm not comfortable with it,I don't have to be involved.
- 所有的事情都找上我  - 她人好好，我真想念她
- It's totally up to me. - She is so great. I miss her.
- 她所谓的“加入”代表什么? - 你的阶段性工作已经完成了
- What does she mean by "involved"? - Your job is done.
也是最有意思的阶段哦
And the most enjoyable.
菲比，说点什么
Phoebe,say something.
她们要我去做超音波检查
They want me to go down to this sonogram thing..
明天和她们两个一起
with them tomorrow.
记得当生活变得简单了…
Remember when life was simpler..
她也不过是个女同性恋了
and she was just a lesbian?
这就是生活啊
Those were the days.
- 你打算怎么做?  - 我也不知道
- What are you gonna do? - I have no idea.
不管我怎么做,我还是孩子的父亲
No matter what I do,I'm still gonna be a father.
面还是被搅乱了，不是吗?
This is still ruined,right?
玛莎路金的女儿会打电话给你
Martha Lugwin's daughter is gonna call you.
- 怎么会有咖喱味?  - 因为有放咖喱?
- What's that curry taste? - Curry.
这东西很好吃，真的
I think they're great. I really do.
你还记得路金一家人吧?  路金很惦记你
The big Lugwin had a thing for you.
- 他们一家都很惦记你.  - 不要这样,妈妈
- They all had a thing for him. - Oh,Mom.
抱歉，她为何要打电话给我?
Why is this girl going to call me?
她刚毕业,想找份烹饪的工作吧
She just graduated,and she wants to be something in cooking or food..
我告诉她你开了一家餐馆
I told her you have a restaurant
-我没开餐馆,只是在餐馆工作  -他们不需要知道
- I don't have,I work in a restaurant. - They don't have to know that.
- 罗斯，能帮我做意大利面吗?  - 好的
- Ross,help me with the spaghetti. - Yes.
我们吃意大利面呀?太简单了
Oh,we're having spaghetti. That's easy.
我们本来要吃意大利烤宽面的
We were going to have lasagna.
- 我喜欢意大利烤宽面  - 不过现在没有了
- I love lasagna. - We're not having it.
那为什么要提到这个呢？这下他就来劲了啊
Then why bring it up? He latches on.
我知道这样要求过于自私
This will sound unbelievably selfish..
你能不能和他们说一下 小孩或女同性恋之类的事?
but did you plan to bring up the baby/lesbian thing?
因为这样可以让我喘口气
It might take the heat off of me.
那个瑞秋…我们在俱乐部碰到了她父母
That Rachel. We saw her parents at the club.
他们很不开心
They were not playing well.
我不想讲他们为此婚礼花了些什么
I won't say what they spent..
但是4万块不是个小数目?
but $40,000 is a lot for a wedding.
至少她有机会把一个男人留在教堂里的圣坛
At least she had the chance to leave a man at the altar.
- 什么意思?  - 没什么
- What's that supposed to mean? - Nothing.
- 随便说说而已  - 不，不是的
- It's an expression. - No,it's not.
别听你妈乱讲话,你一直都很独立
Don't listen to her. You've always been independent.
就连你小时候胖嘟嘟的
Even when you were a chubby kid..
一个朋友也没有的时候，你还是活得好好的
and you had no friends,you were just fine.
你会待在你房里看书…玩拼图
You'd read alone in your room. Your puzzles..
而像罗斯这种人则追求卓越
People like Ross need to shoot for the stars.
博物馆，出版论文…
With his museum and his published papers.
其他人则安于现状
Others are satisfied with staying where they are.
告诉你，这种人不会得癌症
These people never get cancer.
他们对拥有的一切都很开心
They're happy with what they have,content..
就像奶牛一样
like cows.
奶牛，爸爸？
Cows,Dad?
她知道我有多喜欢奶牛
She knows how much I love cows.
我还知道这些女人想拥有一切，幸好
I read about women trying to have it all,and I thank God..
我们家的小口琴（与莫妮卡拼写相近）没有这种问题
our "Harmonica" doesn't have that problem.
- 我跟你说，你很不错  - 谢谢，老爸
- I'm telling you,you'll be fine. - Thank you,Daddy.
天哦，这个居然还能用
Oh,so this does work.
罗斯，最近你怎么样？
So,Ross,what's going on with you?
最近有什么新闻八卦之类可以和老爸老妈分享的
Any stories? No news,no little anecdotes to share with the folks?
好吧,我知道你们想了解
Look,I realize you guys have been wondering..
我和卡萝之间倒底怎么了
what exactly happened between Carol and me.
事情是这样的
And so,well,here's the deal.
卡萝是个女同志
Carol's a lesbian.
她和一个名叫苏珊的女人同居
She lives with a woman named Susan.
她怀了我的孩子
She's pregnant with my child.
并打算和苏珊共同扶养
She and Susan are going to raise the baby.
这些你全都知道?
And you knew about this?
你的状况真的很糟糕吗?
Folks are really that bad?
你要知道这些人十分专业
Well,you know,these people are pros.
他们知道他们要做什么
They know what they do.
他们会躲在那里,再来个突然袭击
They take their time. They get the job done.
常言道：父母是无法交换的
They say that you can't change your parents.
如果可以，我要你的父母
Boy,if you could,I'd want yours.
我要去尿尿了
Must pee.
如果你是双胞胎情况会更惨
It's worse when you're twins.
-你是双胞胎?  -对，我们不往来
- You're a twin? - We don't speak.
她是一心追求事业的人
She's this high-powered,driven,career-type.
-她从事什么工作?  -服务生
- What does she do? - She's a waitress.
- 你们俩长的一样吗？  - 大家都说我俩长的很像
- Identical? - People say we look alike.
但我不这么认为
But I don't see it.
各位，我得打扫了
You guys,I kind of gotta clean up now.
钱德，你是独子?你没有这些困扰?
Chandler,as an only child,you don't have this.
没有，尽管我有个想像中的朋友
No,although I did have an imaginary friend..
而我爸妈比较喜欢他
who my parents preferred.
帮我关灯
Hit the lights,please.
我在里面多久了?
How long was I in there?
- 我只是在打扫  - 需要帮忙吗?
- I'm just cleaning up. - Oh,you need any help?
好呀，谢了
Okay,sure. Thanks.
总之.
Anyway..
明天要见贝瑞，紧张吗?
So you nervous about Barry tomorrow?
有一点
A little.
很紧张
A lot.
有什么建议吗?
So,got any advice?
就一个最近刚被甩的人而言
You know,as someone who's recently been dumped.
你应该避免用“甩”这个字眼
You may wanna steer clear of the word "dumped."
更不巧的是现在他可能痛不欲生
Chances are he's gonna be this broken shell of a man.
因此你不该显得艳光照人,我知道这一点很难做到
You should try not to look too terrific. I know it'll be hard.
这样吧，我拿戒指还贝瑞
Or I'll go down there,and I'll give Barry back his ring.
你陪卡萝及苏珊去做检查
And you can go with Carol and Susan to the ob-gyn.
你明天得见卡萝
You've got Carol tomorrow.
- 此事何时变得这么复杂?  - 你可问倒我了
- When did it get so complicated? - Got me.
-还记得我们在高中时代吗?  -记得
- Remember being in high school? - Yeah.
你没想过自己会遇见心上人
Didn't you think you'd meet someone..
恋爱,然后厮守终生吗?
fall in love,and that'd be it?
- 罗斯?  - 在.在
- Ross? - Yes. Yes.
没想到自己会沦落到这个地步
Man,I never thought I'd be here.
我也是
Me neither.
抱歉，我迟到了,我忙得无法脱身于
Sorry I'm late. I got stuck at work.
那些大的恐龙之类的事情
There was this big dinosaur thing. Anyway..
嗨
Hi.
- 罗斯，记得苏珊吗?  - 我怎能忘得了?
- You remember Susan. - How could I forget?
你好，苏珊，她的手好有力啊…
Hello,Susan. Good shake,good shake.
那么我们在等…
So,we're just waiting for?
- 欧伯曼大夫  - 他…？
- Dr. Oberman. - And is he?
- 是“她” - 当然是…她
- She. - Of course,"she."
她了解我们的特殊状况?
Is she familiar with our special situation?
- 了解，而且她非常支持 - 这太好了
- Yes,and she's very supportive. - Okay,that's great.
不,我只是
No,I'm Oh.
谢了
Thanks.
罗斯，那是用来打开我的子宫颈的
That opens my cervix.
- 贝瑞  - 进来吧
- Barry? - Come on in.
- 可以吗？ - 没问题
- Are you sure? - It's fine.
罗比得待在这儿好几个小时
Robbie's gonna be here for hours.
最近好吗?
So,how are you doing?
我…
I'm..
我很好
I'm okay.
- 你的气色好极了  - 是的
- You look great. - Yeah,well.
法伯大夫，杰森有作呕反应
Dr. Farber,Jason Greenspan's gagging.
马上到,我马上回来
Be right there. Be back in a second.
我甩了他
I dumped him.
事情会如何发展?
So,how's this all gonna work?
婴儿在母亲身体中一个特殊的部位生长
The baby grows in a special place inside
谢谢
Thank you.
我说，我们该如何处理此事?你知道的…
I mean,how's this gonna work,you know,with us?
比方说某些重大的决定
When important decisions have to be made?
- 举个例子  - 我也说不上来
- Give me a "for instance." - Well,I don't know.
- 比方说孩子的名字  - 马龙
- How about with the baby's name? - Marlon.
如果是个男孩马龙,如果是个女孩就叫米妮
If it's a boy. Minnie,if it's a girl.
和米老鼠的女友同名?
As in "Mouse"?
和我奶奶同名
As in my grandmother.
不管怎样,听到这个还是想到老鼠
Still,you say "Minnie," you hear "Mouse."
这个怎么样…？
How about..?
朱莉亚？
How about Julia?
- 朱莉亚  - 我们决定用米妮
- Julia. - We agreed on Minnie.
真幽默，我们曾决定共同生活一辈子
We agreed we'd spend our lives together.
世事难料，兵来将挡
Things change. Roll with the punches.
朱莉亚，就这么决定
I believe Julia's on the table?
抱歉
Sorry about that.
近来可好?
So,what have you been up to?
混得过去
Oh,not much.
- 我刚找到工作  - 这太好了
- I got a job. - That's great.
你为何晒得这么黑?
Why are you so tan?
我去阿鲁巴了
I went to Aruba.
你自己一个去渡蜜月?
Oh,no. You went on our honeymoon alone?
不是的
No.
我和…
I went with..
- 你也许会很不好受  - 我?
- Now,this may hurt. - Me?
不
No.
我和明蒂去了
I went with Mindy.
明蒂?
Mindy?
我的伴娘明蒂?
My maid of honor,Mindy?
对，我们现在有关系了
Yeah,we're kind of a thing now.
你去做植发了?
You got plugs!
小心，还不固定
Careful. They haven't quite taken yet.
你还配了隐形眼镜?
And you got lenses.
你讨厌将手指放进眼睛里
You hate sticking your finger in your eye.
不讨厌她的手
Not for her.
我真的得感谢你
Listen,I really wanted to thank you.
好
Okay.
一个月前我想伤害你,我从未如此激动过
A month ago,I wanted to hurt you more than I've ever wanted to.
我是个整牙医师
And I'm an orthodontist.
你说得没错,我以为我们会过得很快乐
You know,you were right. I thought we were happy.
我们不快乐
We weren't happy.
但是和明蒂在一起
But with Mindy..
现在我很快乐
now I'm happy.
-吐掉  -什么?
- Spit. - What?
我
Me.
总之
Anyway..
这东西属于你的,或许以后是明蒂的
I guess this belongs to you. Or maybe some day Mindy.
她会勉强接受的
Like she'd settle for that.
是的，看来是真的
Yeah,that's true.
我觉得这是一个不错的戒指
But I think it's a nice ring..
谢谢你送我
and thank you for giving it to me.
谢谢你送还给我
Thank you for giving it back.
喂!
Hello!
- 拜托，海伦有什么不好?  - 海伦盖勒?
- Please,what's wrong with Helen? - Helen Geller?
- 不行  - 她不会叫海伦盖勒的
- I don't think so. - It's not gonna be Helen Geller.
- 谢谢 - 不，我是说她不姓盖勒
- Thank you. - No,I mean,it's not Geller.
难道她叫海伦威利克
It'll be Helen Willick?
老实说,我们考虑用海伦威利克班奇
No,actually,we talked about Helen Willick Bunch.
等等，为何有她的份?
Wait a minute. Why is she in the title?
因为她也是我的宝宝
It's my baby too.
真的?我不记得女人也会制造精子
Really? I don't remember you making any sperm.
我们都知道那是个极大的挑战
And we all know what a challenge that is.
-你们两个，别吵了  -不，功劳全让她抢了,我也在场
- You two,stop it. - She gets a credit. I'm in there too.
你不会想用海伦威利克班奇盖勒吧?这有虐待儿童之嫌
Helen Willick Bunch Geller? I think that borders on child abuse.
当然没有,我想用盖勒威利克班奇
Of course not. I'm suggesting Geller Willick Bunch.
绝对不行,你看他,没人会叫她全名的
See what he does? He knows no one's gonna say all those names.
他知道别人只会叫她盖勒  这样他就得逞了
They'll call her Geller. He gets his way.
我得逞?你认为这样算我得逞?
My way? You think this is my way?
相信我，我没想到自己会沦落到这种地步
Of all the ways I ever imagined this moment being..
我是不得已的…这很辛苦的
this is not my You know what? This is too hard.
有人在吗? 今天如何，想呕吐吗?
Knock,knock. How are we? Any nausea?
- 一点点  - 只是一点点
- A little. - Just a little.
我只是问准妈妈,很感谢你们的分享
I was wondering about the mother-to-be,but thanks for sharing.
- 躺好  - 知道吗?我不加入
- Lie back. - You know what? I'm gonna go.
我认为此时自己无法进入这个家庭了
I don't think I can be involved in this family thing.
- 我的天呀  - 快看啊
- Oh,my God! - Look at that.
我知道
I know.
很神奇吧
Well,isn't that amazing?
我们该看什么?
What are we supposed to be seeing here?
我不知道，可能是要攻击进取号(《星际迷航》)
I don't know,but I think it's about to attack the Enterprise.
如果你们把头稍微向左偏，两眼放轻松
If you tilt your head and relax your eyes..
它样子就像是一个颗老马铃薯
it kind of looks like an old potato.
那么就不要那么干
Then don't do that,all right?
莫妮卡，你认为呢?
Monica,what do you think?
- 你热泪盈眶  - 才没有
- Are you welling up? - No.
-你有，你热泪盈眶 -我没有
- You are. You're welling up. - I'm not.
- 你就要成为阿姨了  - 闭嘴
- You're gonna be an aunt. - Oh,shut up.
明蒂，我是瑞秋
Hi,Mindy. Hi,it's Rachel.
我很好，我今天和贝瑞见面了
Yeah,I'm fine. I saw Barry today.
对，他告诉我了 不，没关系，真的
Yeah,he told me. No,it's okay. Really,it's okay.
我祝福你们幸福快乐,真心诚意的
I hope you two are very happy. I really do.
如果一切顺利
And,Min,you know,if everything works out..
你们结婚生子
and you guys get married and have kids..
希望他们有像他那样的头发和你的鼻子
I hope they have his hairline and your nose!
我知道这招很贱，但我感觉好棒
That was a cheap shot,but I feel so much better now!